Kazuma!
和真
I am Kazuma.
我是和真
How embarrassing. You actually died.
你居然死了 真丢脸
You're so excited.
你的兴致真高昂呢
I have always wanted to say it once.
我一直想说一次看看
Kazuma!
和真
I am Kazuma.
我是和真
Your body has been revived!
你的身体已经复活了
Come back quickly!
快回来吧
Darkness is really sad for no reason
身上一股酸臭味的达克妮丝
and has a bad smell.
不知道为什么超沮丧的
Come back quickly, come back!
你快回来啦 快回来
Mr. Kazuma, welcome back.
和真先生 欢迎你回来
It stinks!
好臭
What happened to my clothes?
我的衣服呢
It's all melted.
全都溶掉了哦
Only this strangely named sword is left.
只有这把名字很怪的刀还留着
What?
什么
The name I chose for the sword is strange, you say?
居然说我帮刀取的名字很怪
I can't just listen to that.
我可不能听听就算了
Darkness.
达克妮丝
Lady Eris told me about it.
我听艾莉丝大人说了哦
To save me,
你为了救我
you got eaten by the water snake?
自己被水蛇吞掉了吗
That is not like you at all.
真是的 一点也不像你
Okay, let us go home and take a bath immediately.
好了 我们快点回家洗澡吧
Hey, Kazuma.
我说和真
It does not seem right to ask her to take a bath
你用那个模样邀请她洗澡
when you are not dressed.
好像不太好
Are you a pervert?
你是变态吗
(Konosuba S3)
《为美好的世界献上祝福！ 第三季》
(Episode 8: Eternal Rest to The Lord of This Lake) Okay, quickly take a bath.
(第8集 为这个湖的主人献上永眠) 好了 你们快点去洗澡吧
Kazuma, if you keep dressing like that,
和真穿成这样
people will call the cops.
别人会报警的
Shut up!
吵死了
There is no need to worry about that water snake over there, right?
水蛇那边没问题吧
It should be busy polluting the lake water for now.
它应该会暂时忙着污染湖水
I am the one who purified the lake.
净化湖水是我的功劳哦
Aqua, when you are overconfident,
阿库娅自信满满的时候
a trap is likely to be lurking around.
八成都有什么陷阱
Geez, I can't stand you.
真是的 真受不了你
If you continue to utter crazy things,
要是你继续说奇怪的话
I will have Kazuma or Darkness carry you.
我就让和真或达克妮丝背你哦
I apologize, please don't do that!
我向你道歉 请别这么做
Please!
拜托你
Then let's go.
那我们走吧
We should do our best to show off our accomplishments to other people.
我们要尽量向别人炫耀我们的表现
Therefore, we could get some money
这么一来 就算拿不到讨伐奖金
even if we do not get the prize for being subdued.
至少也能得到一笔钱
Leave it to me!
包在我身上
Let me tell you more
我的爆裂魔法究竟有多厉害
about how strong my explosion magic is!
就让我仔细说说吧
Aqua told me that
听阿库娅说
the water snake who ate me
被水蛇消化的我
seems to have turned me into a baby Kazuma.
好像变成了小和真
It should have gone back to its original size, right?
应该有恢复成原本的大小吧
Kazuma.
和真
Yes?
是
I'm baby Kazuma.
我是小和真
You took a long bath.
你洗得真久
Could it be that you are hurting?
难道是哪里痛吗
I-I'm fine.
我…我没事
It smells awful, do not you think?
你想想 味道不是很臭吗
That is why I wanted to wash it off well.
所以我想仔细洗干净
Hey, Kazuma.
我说和真
Um…
那个
I am sorry that my request this time was too much.
抱歉我这次提出无理的要求
Stop talking about the past.
过去的事就别提了
Aqua and Megumin are probably eating fancy food at the guild.
比起这个 阿库娅她们八成在公会吃美食
Let us hurry over too.
我们也快点过去吧
Alright, you're right.
好啊 说得也是
Then I will leave these clothes here for you to change into.
那我把替换的衣服放在这里
Hey.
我说你
Do you need to beat water snake for some reason?
难道有非打倒水蛇不可的理由吗
Wha--
什…
No!
什么都没有
-It seems there is a reason. -No, how could there be?
-看来有啊 -没有 怎么可能有
Despite failing today,
虽然今天没有成功
let us plan ahead for the next time
但下次去挑战那只水蛇的时候
we try to beat that water snake.
我们先拟好战略再去吧
What's up with you?
什么啊
You made a big deal out
你明明大言不惭
of saying you would keep people safe,
说要保护人民的安全
but you gave up so fast.
结果却这么快就放弃了吗
Idiot, who do you think I am?
笨蛋 你以为我是谁啊
It is the duty
保护人民
of the Dustiness family to safeguard the populace!
就是达斯堤尼斯家被赋予的使命
I will kill that water snake the next time!
下次我一定会杀了那只水蛇
Why are you so prone to doing pointless things?
为什么你们老是做些多余的事啊
You dare to anger the fierce water snake!
竟然随便惹怒水蛇那种狠角色
Oh my, Megumin!
惠惠真是的
Do you have any idea what kind of trouble you got into?
你到底闯了什么祸啊
Kazuma!
和真
Why are they mad?
为什么他们会生气啊
Were we not supposed to vanquish it
我们不是应该在骑士团来之前
with a determination to perish before the knights came?
抱着必死的决心讨伐它吗
Because something very big happened in the royal capital.
其实是因为王都发生了大案子
The royal capital?
王都吗
Brother.
哥哥
Hey, is the royal capital in danger?
喂 王都有危险吗
Is my dear sister in danger?
我可爱的妹妹身陷危机吗
The royal castle has been broken into by a group of thieves
好像有个叫银发盗贼团的家伙们
called the Silver-Haired Thieves.
潜入了王城
The knights have been sent to catch them
因为他们偷走了宝物
because they stole treasures.
所以骑士团被派去追捕他们
How is this possible?
怎么会这样
I am also being sought after along with the leaders of the Devil King Army.
继魔王的干部后 我也被悬赏了
If this city gets
王都的通缉令
the royal capital's wanted order, it means…
特地发来这座城市就代表…
I am only telling you this.
偷偷告诉你们
They asked a fortune-teller from the Crimson Demon Village
他们请红魔之里的占卜师
to help them figure out where the criminal is.
帮忙占卜犯人下落的结果
-The target with a 200 million reward - No…it's not like that.
-没想到价值两亿的悬赏目标 -不…不是啦
-is surprisingly in Axel City. -Don't make such a scary face.
-就在这座阿克塞尔城市 -别露出这么可怕的表情
200 million?
两亿?
Hey, is that true?
喂 真的吗
That must make more money than killing monsters.
这比讨伐怪物还要有赚头吧
Exactly.
就是说啊
-The Silver-Haired Thieves -We really need money, so we have to do it.
-我们正好缺钱 只能上了啊 -那…那个银发盗贼团
are in this city?
就在这座城市?
200 million Eris…
两亿艾莉丝…
200 million Eris, huh?
两亿艾莉丝吗
Hey, why are you looking at me?
喂 你干嘛看我啊
If you capture the Silver-Haired Thieves,
各位 只要抓到银发盗贼团
the knights can come to Axel and conquer the water snake.
骑士团就能来阿克塞尔讨伐水蛇了
That's how it is.
就是这样
We need your help, Mr. Kazuma.
麻烦和真先生帮忙了
O-Of course, I'll help.
我…我当然会帮忙啦
Good night, dragon.
晚安 龙
-My plan is to hide at home, of course. -Good dragon.
-我当然要躲在家里 -乖巧的龙
After you are born,
等你出生后
-I will raise you. -Hey, what are you doing?
-喂 那是在干嘛 -我就会养你
Prenatal education.
胎教啊
Right?
对吧
There is no need for you to keep looking after it.
用不着一直顾着蛋也无所谓吧
It should stay warm if you put it in front of the stove, right?
只要放在暖炉前 把它弄暖就行了吧
You can eat it as a snack if it gets too done.
烤过头的话就做成点心吃掉
Hey!
喂
Be careful, or I'll feed you a sacred punch!
小心我喂你吃神圣的拳头哦
I am giving it magical power.
我是在注入魔力
He's going to be the leader of the dragon.
它是要成为群龙之首的人物
I want to give it everything
作为养育它的母亲
because I am its mother.
我想为它付出一切
Right, Jelteman?
对吧 爵尔帝
You really did pick such a bad name.
竟然取这种乱七八糟的名字
Kazuma!
和真
The key is firepower!
关键是火力
We should fight until the water snake is gone
如果不能一次击沉水蛇
if we cannot get rid of it in one shot.
那就打到它消失就好
What?
什么
Like when we were fighting the mobile fortress destroyer.
就像机动要塞毁灭者战时那样
With Aqua's power
只要有阿库娅的魔力
and Kazuma's Drain Touch, we can defeat it.
跟和真的Drain Touch就能办到
I don't want to.
我不要
Huh?
咦
Why do I have to take this dirty Lich skill?
为什么我非得接受 肮脏的巫妖技能不可啊
I can't just give away
我的神圣魔力
my holy magical power to anyone.
不能随随便便给任何人
I am not going to do it,
就算和真威胁我
not even if Kazuma threatens me,
或达克妮丝纵容我
Darkness treats me well,
还是惠惠发神经
or Megumin goes crazy!
我都绝对不做
Huh?
咦
So, Megumin,
话说回来
why do you want to get back at it so badly?
为什么连惠惠都这么想雪耻啊
Because it killed you.
因为它是杀了和真的对手
Naturally, I want to get revenge on it personally.
我当然想亲自报仇啦
I-I see.
这…这样啊
From then on,
在那之后我每天
I used Darkness's Decoy,
都利用达克妮丝的诱饵技能
cast Explosion on it, and then ran away
对它施展爆裂魔法再逃走
every day to bother it.
不断骚扰它
Couldn't we find a more effective solution?
难道没有其他更好的对付手段吗
Darkness, what are you doing?
达克妮丝 你在做什么啊
Shouldn't you be the one to stop her now?
这种时候阻止她是你的工作吧
B-But…
可…可是
No matter what, I want to beat that water snake.
我无论如何都想打倒那只水蛇
Also, this makes water snake's magic less strong.
而且这样也能削弱水蛇的魔力
These two…
这两个家伙…
Anyway,
不管怎样
it is not going to happen while it is still raining, right?
只要还在下雨就没办法吧
It would only be good for it.
只会对它有利而已
The weather report says it will rain for a while longer.
天气预报说雨还会下一阵子
I will get serious when the weather gets better.
等天气放晴后我就会认真做
Do you mean you are not going to be serious now?
也就是说 你暂时都不会拿出干劲咯
What are you doing? Stop it!
你干嘛啦 住手
Give Chomusuke back to me!
把豆之助还给我
Bastard, let go of it quickly!
混蛋 快放开它
Believe it or not, I will hurt you if you do not let go!
不放开的话 我就让你吃苦头哦
-It kept raining for days on end. -Explosion, explosion.
-后来过了好几天 雨都没停 -爆裂 爆裂
Darkness and Megumin were the only ones
只有达克妮丝和惠惠两个人
-who kept going after the water snake. - Explosion, explosion.
-一直去找水蛇 -爆裂 爆裂
We're home.
我们回来了
Darkness is in a pretty messy state.
达克妮丝搞得很狼狈
Please take her to bathe.
麻烦带她去洗澡
It's too dangerous. You guys shouldn't go there anymore.
太危险了 你们还是别再去那里了
That snake
那家伙
sneaked up on us, maybe because it can't stand
不知道是不是受不了 连日来的爆裂魔法
the constant explosion.
竟然偷袭我们
Megumin just barely used magic to hit it.
惠惠好不容易用魔法击中它
During its process of neck regeneration, we managed to flee.
我们趁它脖子再生的时候逃回来
It is really hard to deal with.
它果然不好对付啊
Aqua, thank you.
阿库娅 谢谢你
You are a dragon.
你是龙
An awesome dragon.
很棒的龙
But your mom, who is me,
但是妈妈
-Kazuma, what are you doing? - is blue.
-和真 你在做什么 -是蓝色的哦
I'm fixing it for you since I have too much time on my hands.
我太闲了 所以在帮你修理
-It's raining outside anyway. -Even with the padding,
-反正外面在下雨 -塞了胸垫的艾莉丝
-I have nothing to do, either.
-我也没事可做
-Don't go back there after I fixed it, okay? -Eris's breast remains flat.
-你可别因为修好了又跑去哦 -胸部还是很平
When we went to
这么说起来
the hot springs together,
大家一起去泡温泉的时候
you also helped me repair my armor, didn't you?
你也在途中帮我修过盔甲吧
I would like to go to the hot springs with you guys again.
我还想再跟大家一起去泡温泉
I don't want to.
我可不要
I hate that city.
我讨厌那座城市
Everyone there is as strange as Megumin.
那里有很多跟惠惠一样怪异的人
Hey, what do you mean by that?
喂 怪异是什么意思
Let's be clear about this.
给我说清楚
Hey.
喂
What is up with saying such hurtful things
你怎么能对我可爱的信徒们
about my cute believers?
说这种过分的话啊
Aqua, how can you say that?
连阿库娅都这么说
What on earth do you mean? Let's be clear about this.
到底是什么意思 给我说清楚
My believers
我的信徒们
are all earnest and well-behaved.
都是非常认真又乖巧的好孩子
-Are you implying -Despite this,
-你的意思是 -即使如此
-that I am not earnest and well-behaved? -I still want to go.
-我不是认真又乖巧的好孩子吗 -我还是想再去
Kazuma, Darkness has disappeared!
和真 达克妮丝不见了
She vanished along with her armor!
她和装备一起消失了
That fellow…
那家伙
I told her not to go!
我明明一直叫她不要去
It is too perilous to go alone!
一个人去太危险了
Really!
真是的
She is really a pain.
她也很让人头痛
I will leave Wiz to take care of the egg.
我把蛋交给维兹保管
Let's go teach Darkness a lesson.
去教训达克妮丝一下
Go stop Darkness first, Aqua and Megumin.
阿库娅和惠惠先去阻止达克妮丝
How about you?
你呢
I have to go somewhere.
我要先去一个地方
We can't let her fight by herself.
绝对不能让她一个人战斗哦
Damn her.
真是的 那家伙
She makes me mad!
真拿她没办法
Ominous sky.
不祥的天色
My old wounds have begun to hurt.
我的旧伤开始痛了
Let me go!
放开我
Seriously, I can't stand you!
真是的 真受不了你
You can't do it alone.
你一个人是办不到的
You do not want to go back halfway
你以为会被骂
because you think we will scold you?
所以不敢中途回去吗
I am not going to get mad. Come on, go back.
我不会生气的 回去吧
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
你到底怎么了
We have teamed up.
我们是伙伴
Tell us the reason.
告诉我们理由吧
I…
我…
Even if it is not possible…
就算办不到…
Darkness.
达克妮丝
Hey, wait for us.
喂 等等我们
What's going on?
这是怎么回事
Lalatina!
拉拉蒂娜
Don't call me Lalatina!
别叫我拉拉蒂娜
-What are you doing? -Hey, Lalatina, do not say that.
-你们在闹什么 -别这么说嘛 拉拉蒂娜
-If it is a new trick, -We refuse to let our pal Lalatina
-如果是新的恶作剧方式 -我们不会让拉拉蒂娜小妹
-I have other ideas. -act on her own.
-我也有自己的打算 -自己一个人乱来的
No, it is not it.
不…不是啦
I am merely telling everyone
我只是告诉大家
that you go to deal with the water snake every day
你每天都去对付水蛇
and ask them if they can help.
问他们能不能来帮忙而已
Recently, Kazuma has been buying us dinner a lot.
因为和真最近常常请我们吃饭
We ought to be able to pay him back a little.
稍微还他一点人情也不会遭天谴
After all, we might as well listen to your vague wishes, Lalatina.
顺便听听拉拉蒂娜的任性要求吧
Alright, look.
好了 看清楚咯
So many adventurers have come for you.
有这么多的冒险者为了你而来
We do not like how stubborn you are,
虽然拿你的死脑筋没辙
but you should not worry them.
但你还是别让他们担心啦
Everyone…
各位
Oh my, Lalatina
喂 明明是拉拉蒂娜
is blushing!
居然害羞了
Blessing.
Blessing
Thieves, prepare Bind.
盗贼们负责准备Bind
For archers, get your grappling hook-equipped shots ready.
弓兵们准备绑着钩绳的箭待命
Our opponent is a water snake.
对手是水蛇
Do not be careless, okay?
千万别大意哦
Okay!
好
There is no need for magicians to save a second shot.
魔法师们不需要预留第二发
Gather all your magical might and get ready for a massive one!
注入所有魔力 准备一发大的吧
Leave it to me!
包在我身上
I will definitely employ Explosion
这次我一定要用爆裂魔法
to dispel that water snake this time.
炸飞那只水蛇
And then, Darkness,
然后达克妮丝
your Decoy is the key to victory.
你的诱饵技能是胜负关键
Do not be easily defeated, okay?
可别轻易被打倒哦
Okay.
好
Let's go!
我们上吧
Blessing.
Blessing…
Darkness!
达克妮丝
Leave it to me!
交给我吧
Decoy!
诱饵
I'm going to kill you!
我要杀了你
Good, thieves' skill squad!
好 盗贼技能部队
Bind!
Bind
Go!
上啊…
Thump!
咚
The wind direction is fine.
风向没问题
Visibility is clear.
视野没问题
A bit higher.
再往上一点
That's right.
就是这样
Very good, stop.
很好 停止
Fire!
发射
Got it!
勾住它了
Pull hard, pull hard!
用力拉 用力拉
Harder!
再加把劲
Is this truly okay, Kazuma?
真的没问题吗 和真
Yes, just go for it!
对 尽管放手做吧
Okay!
好
It is impossible to beat until its magic power is gone.
如果它的魔力没耗尽就打不倒
Let me drain it then.
那就由我来吸干吧
Drain Touch!
Drain Touch
We can do it!
办得到
Worked!
有效 有效
Kazuma!
和真
Everyone!
各位
This is really Miss Dustiness.
不愧是达斯堤尼斯小姐
Seriously, you have amazing wrist strength and endurance.
腕力和耐力真不是盖的
Is this the right time to say this?
现在是说这个的时候吗
Things can't go like this
这样子不行
I can't hold on anymore.
我会撑不住的
Idiot, hold on for me!
笨蛋 给我撑住
You have to hold on!
你要撑住
Drain Touch!
Drain Touch
-Every day, Darkness hurts herself -Drain Touch!
-达克妮丝天天让自己受伤 -Drain Touch…
-to lessen this snake magic power.
-削弱这家伙的魔力
-How can I let her work go to waste? -Drain Touch!
-我怎么能让她的努力白费 -Drain Touch…
I can't hold on anymore.
我撑不住了
Hey!
喂
You rarely help, but now you have a chance to shine,
平常派不上用场的你难得大显身手
and then you are out of the game so quickly?
结果这么快就没戏唱了吗
You can't hold on even like this.
这样子就受不了的人
Are you able to win an endurance contest back-to-back?
有办法在忍耐大赛连霸吗
You're such a weakling.
没毅力的家伙
Being scolded by a mean man
在水蛇的重压之下
while being pressed hard by the water snake
被无情的男人斥责
was…
真是…
a truly wonderful reward!
美好的奖励
Pull! Pull!
快拉 快拉
Darkness can't hold on any longer.
达克妮丝要撑不住了
Don't underestimate the adventurers of Axel!
别小看阿克塞尔的冒险者
Everyone…
各位…
Don't worry, Kazuma.
和真 放心吧
I will die with you.
我会跟你一起死
Could I not be worried?
我哪能放心啊
Don't give up!
别放弃
How could you die from being pressed by a water snake when you are so strong?
你这么强壮 怎么可能被水蛇压一下就死
I am the only one who will die from being crushed!
会被压死的只有我一个吧
Wha--
什…
Kazuma is going to die if I give up now?
如果我放弃 和真就会死?
What is this feeling?
这是什么感觉
Although you act like my lord and urge me to hold on,
虽然你像主人般命令我撑住
your life is in my hands.
但你的性命却掌握在我手里
What a contradiction.
这种矛盾…
Who really is the lord in this case?
现在这种情况 到底谁才是主人
This is something new for me.
感觉好新鲜
This is something new for me, Kazuma!
和真 感觉好新鲜
Has the water snake weakened?
水蛇那家伙是不是变弱了啊
I will take the heavyweight reward target!
重量级悬赏目标就由我收下了
The reward money goes to the person who kills it!
杀死它的人能拿走所有奖金
Hey, what are you talking about?
喂 这种情况下你在说什么啊
I won't share with anyone--
我不会分给任何…
Duster!
达斯特
Light of Saber!
Light of Saber
Hey, look!
喂 你们看
Its head is not growing back.
它的头没有再生
Magicians!
各位魔法师
The sound of impending doom,
渐渐逼近的叹息
the cries that will soon erupt,
宣泄而出的呐喊
-is the roar that will guide us to triumph. -Get out of here before the explosion happens!
-那是引领我们迈向胜利的吼叫 -爆裂魔法要来了 快疏散
The smoke of the end
终结的狼烟
is rising right now.
此刻在这里升起吧
And it will soon transform into a bouquet
变成祭祀的花束
to be offered to him in heaven as an offering.
献给在天堂的他
I want to avenge Kazuma!
我要帮和真报仇
Hey, I'm still alive, you know!
喂 我还活着哦
Explosion!
爆裂魔法
But I didn't think
不过
it would really work out.
没想到真的船到桥头自然直呢
Give Kazuma and his friends a little extra bonus, okay?
要多给和真他们一点奖金哦
I truly hope they can seize the urge to monopolize the bonus
真希望他们能把想独吞奖金
and take away the portion of that guy who wanted to flee.
自己偷跑的垃圾的份也拿走
It might be best not to let him revive at all.
干脆就那样别让他复活更好吧
How do you feel after defeating the water snake
打倒你心心念念的水蛇
you have been longing for?
感觉怎么样
Can this make you sleep well?
这样你就能安稳睡觉了吗
Yes.
对啊
I no longer have to worry about anything because of you.
多亏了你 我的烦恼都一扫而空了
I am not even sure what I was worrying about.
甚至不知道自己在烦恼什么
I believe that my former self was quite foolish.
觉得很可笑
However, this is not due to defeating the water snake.
但那并不是因为打倒水蛇的关系
-Now I know for sure. -Hey, that's my doing, right?
-我再次意识到 -喂 那是我的功劳吧
-I really do like the people in this place. -It's thanks to Lady Aqua, right?
-自己真的很喜欢这座城市的人们 -是阿库娅大人的功劳吧
-I won't be lost anymore. -You're so crooked.
-我不会再迷惘了 -你好奸诈
You say some stupid things without thinking about it.
你偶尔会若无其事说些丢脸的话耶
Life is good for me.
我是个幸福的人
Hey, show me more respect!
喂 再尊敬我一点
I should be thanked for bringing you back to life.
说阿库娅大人 谢谢你让我复活
Admire me a bit more!
再多佩服我一点啦
Hey, Kazuma!
喂 和真
The priest on your team
从刚刚开始
has been a pain since just now.
你们队里的祭司就一直烦人
-I'm back. -Welcome back.
-我回来了 -欢迎回来
Darkness, are you home?
达克妮丝 你先回来了吗
Oh, she does not seem to be here.
咦 她好像不在呢
She is probably in her room.
应该在房里吧
Okay.
好了
Let us continue drinking in our warm house.
在我们温馨的家里继续喝吧
Hurry and call Darkness over.
快点叫达克妮丝过来
Quickly, call her here.
快叫她过来
Kazuma.
和真
What is this?
这是什么
What?
什么啊
I am sorry I said something…
突然说这样的话…
Hey, this is…
喂 这是…
I am sorry I said something
突然说这样的话
like that out of the blue.
真的很抱歉
Things got really complicated.
发生了一些复杂的事
I realize this is selfish,
我知道这么说很任性
but I want to leave the squad.
但我想退出队伍
Please find someone else to take my place
请你们找个前锋代替我
as the vanguard.
加入队伍吧
I appreciate all of you.
我很感谢你们
No amount of thanking
这份感激之情
will suffice to express my gratitude.
不管说多少次谢谢都不够
Aqua, Megumin, and Kazuma.
阿库娅 惠惠 和真
The excursions I have had with you
和你们一起经历的冒险
have been the happiest times
是我到目前为止的人生里
of my life so far.
最快乐的时光
I shall never forget
我今后肯定
our adventures together.
也忘不了跟你们一起冒险的岁月
Thank you for everything over this period.
一直以来谢谢你们了
From Lalatina Ford Dustiness.
达斯堤尼斯·福特·拉拉蒂娜敬上
A heartfelt thank you
为我深爱的伙伴
to my loving companions.
献上深深的感谢
(Episode 9: Preaching to the Runaway Girl)
(第9集 为离家出走的 女孩献上说教)
This is the very end of the line.
这里是队伍的最尾巴
Hey, stay tuned.
哎嘿 敬请期待
I don't think you understand.
这么说 您应该听不懂吧
I think this is the store's motto for ads…
我把这个当作 店里的广告标语…